Wang Liang

* Phone Number: +86 186 4258 3168

* Email: wbit58@gmail.com

* Skype: live:wbit85

* Address: Sanhao St, 35/2, ShenYang, LiaoNing, China, 110000

Birthday : May 1, 1985

* Github: https://github.com/nkhs* Gitlab: https://gitlab.com/nkhs

* Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/wang-liang-2a268a15a/

* Stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/11343720/king-stone

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I received a Master's degree from Hong Kong University of Science and Technology and I've been working as a web developer for 10 years.

I am confident in the issues raised in a certain field and have a hobby in researching new technologies.

In relation to other people, we value intimacy and do not give up what we started, regardless of profitability.

CORE SKILLS

- Angular 6+, Angular PWA, Angular Material, Angular CLI
- React.js, React-Bootstrap/Material-UI/Semantic-UI, Styled Component, Postcss, CSS module, Next.js, ReactXP, Ant Design
- Javascript, Typescript, Flow, ES6/7

- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, SASS/LESS, Jade, etc.
- MEAN/MERN
- Node.js/Express.js
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL
- AWS (EC2, Lambda, DynamoDB, S3, etc), Heroku, Firebase

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (WEB DEVELOPMENT)

Dalian Daxian Group Co., Ltd., October 2011 - April 2014

- Excellent communication including the ability to distill technical details into human terms
- -Solid knowledge of JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and browser APIs
- -Solid knowledge of at least one of the following programming languages: Java, JavaScript, C#
- Highly capable in Node JS or Java with the desire to learn new languages
- Experience designing and implementing RESTful services, good knowledge of HTTP specifics
- -Attention to details, high standards for quality
- Highly developed oral and written communication skills; strong presentation skills

MEAN STACK DEVELOPER

santawi.cn, JUN 2014 - MAY 2020

- Started for Angular 2+ frontend project, and design(Bootstrap UI, Material UI)
- After 6 months, take part in backend(Node) developing for Interaction with frontend, and related techniques: NodeJS/Express/NPM, Mongo/Cloud, WebRTC/Socket/MQTT, ...

EDUCATION

THE HONG KONG UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY. 2007-2010

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer and Information Sciences, Software Management

TRAINING

- English Course, 2009-2012
- Research and Development Training, 2008~2009
- Samsung Core Network CDMA System (Legacy MSC) Training, 2013
- Project Management (PMI) course at XL Axiata, 2012~2015

AWARDS

- 2013 The "New PHD Researcher Award" by Chinese Ministry of Education.
- 2013 Winner of ther 2011 ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest.
- 2004 Awarded in the 38th Chinese Coding Contest.
- 2005 Gold Medal of the 41th LiaoNing Childrens' Mathematical Contest.

LANGUAGES

- Chinese Native
- English Fluent